That's the case in general.
그것은 일반적으로 그렇습니다.
If you have N inputs, and K outputs,
you have (N+1)K parameters to use.
N 개의 입력과 K 개의 출력을 가지고 있다면,
사용할 (N + 1) K 개의 매개 변수가 있습니다.
Not one more.
하나도 없어요.
The thing is, you might want to use
many, many more parameters in practice.
사실, 실제로 더 많은 매개 변수를 사용하는 것이 좋습니다.
Also, it's linear.
또한 선형입니다.
This means that the kind of interactions
that you're capable of representing with
이것은 당신이 그 모델로 표현할 수있는 상호 작용의 종류가
that model is somewhat limited.
다소 제한된다는 것을 의미합니다.
For example, if two inputs
interact in an additive way,
예를 들어, 두 입력이 부가적인 방식으로 상호 작용하는 경우,
your model can represent them
well as a matrix multiply.
여러의 모델은 행렬 곱셈으로 잘 나타낼 수 있습니다.
But if two inputs interact in the way
that the outcome depends on the product
그러나 두 입력이 상호 작용하는 경우 예를 들어 두 모델의
of the two for
결과에 따라 결과가
example, you won't be able to model
that efficiently with a linear model.
달라 지므로 선형 모델로 효율적으로 모델링 할 수 없습니다.
Linear operations
are really nice though.
선형 작업은 정말 좋습니다.
Big matrix multiplies are exactly
what GPUs were designed for.
큰 행렬 곱셈은 정확하게 GPU가 설계된 것입니다.
They're relatively cheap and
very, very fast.
그들은 상대적으로 저렴하고 매우 빠르고 매우 빠릅니다.
Numerically linear
operations are very stable.
수치 적 선형 연산은 매우 안정적입니다.
We can show mathematically that
small changes in the input
우리는 수학적으로 입력에 작은 변화가 있음을 보여줄 수 있습니다.
can never yield big
changes in the output.
출력에서 큰 변화를 결코 가져올 수 없다.
The derivates are very nice too.
미분도 매우 좋습니다.
The derivative of a linear
function is constant.
선형 함수의 미분은 일정합니다.
You can't get more stable
numerically than a constant.
상수보다 더 안정적으로 수치를 얻을 수 없습니다.
So, we would like to keep our parameters
inside big linear functions, but
따라서 우리는 매개 변수를 큰 선형 함수 내부에 유지 하려고 하지만
we would also want the entire
model to be nonlinear.
전체 모델이 비선형이기를 원할 것입니다.
We can't just keep multiplying
our inputs by linear functions,
선형 함수로 입력 값을 계속 곱할 수는 없습니다.
because that's just equivalent
to one big linear function.
이것은 하나의 큰 선형 함수와 동일하기 때문입니다.
So, we're going to have to
introduce non-linearities.
그래서 우리는 비선형 성을 도입해야 할 것입니다.